Edgar Mejia Razo

Software, Electronics & Telecommunications Engineer

PROFILE

Software, Electronics and Telecommunications Engineer with over 4 years of experience in network solutions interested in expanding my career with a software development position where my thinking and programming skills contribute to the objectives of the company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

12/2019-Present Package Handler

Fedex Ground. Toronto, ON.

 Physical load and unload of packages by hand, including placing, pushing, lifting, carrying and pulling items in an efficient and safe manner.

01/2020-

Seasonal Retail Team Member

Centennial College Bookstore. Toronto, ON.

 Greeted customers, responded to questions, fixed and restocked shelves, reviewed inventory and provided outstanding customer service.

08/2019-11/2018

Technical Tendering Specialist

Nokia. Global Services. Mexico City.

 Prepared and overviewed Physical Implementation Services quotations of Telecommunications infrastructure focused on US and Canada accounts.

11/2018-11/2017

Services Solution Specialist/Services Stream Leader

Nokia. Global Services. Mexico City.

 Prepared and overviewed services quotations for Telecommunications infrastructure offers dedicated to Project management, quality control and technical summaries.

11/2017-12/2014

Solution Engineer

Nokia. Global Services. Mexico City.

 Analyzed and consolidated services quotations of new projects.

12/2014-

IT Support Engineer

08/2012

Instituto Nacional de Medicina Genómica INMEGEN. Mexico City.

• Provided IT support for internal users.

EDUCATION

09/2019current Game Programming - Software Engineering.
Advanced Diploma

Centennial College Toronto

12/2014-08/2009 Engineering in Electronic Systems and Telecommunications

Instituto Tecnológico y de Estudios Superiores de Monterrey (ITESM) Campus Ciudad de México.

PERSONAL INFO

Email

edgaradrian.mejiarazo@gmail.com

Address

80 Orchid Place Drive, Toronto, ON M1B OC4

Mobile

(647) 679-1676

PROGRAMMING AND SOFTWARE SKILLS

Troubleshooting in several programming languages and platforms of low and high level as:

- Arduino
- C,C#
- HTML
- Visual Studio
- Python Assembler

Use of computational tools such as:

- Microsoft Office
- Matlab & Simulink
- AVR Studio
- Unity

KEY COMPETENCIES:

- High capacity and ease of adaptation
- Great willingness to learn
- Creative
- Patient
- Pro-active

LANGUAGES

- English, TOEFL IBT 92.
- Spanish, native.

RESEARCH PROJECTS

12/2014-08/2009

Research on Engineering Project in Creation, Analysis and Reproduction of Binaural Sounds and their therapeutic application. Testing and analysis of sound reproducing devices.